[
  {
    "Option a": "0, 1900, 2004, 2005",
    "Option b": "1900, 2004",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "An input field takes the year of birth between 1900 and 2004. The boundary values for testing this field are:",
    "Option c": "1899, 1900, 2004, 2005",
    "Option d": "1899, 1900, 1901, 2003, 2004, 2005"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "System testing",
    "Option b": "Usability testing",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Which one of the following are non-functional testing methods?",
    "Option c": "Performance testing",
    "Option d": "Both b & c"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Data tester",
    "Option b": "Boundary tester",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Which of the following tools would be involved in the automation of regression test?",
    "Option c": "Capture\/Playback",
    "Option d": "Output comparator"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Statement coverage",
    "Option b": "Pole coverage",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Incorrect form of Logic coverage is:",
    "Option c": "Condition coverage",
    "Option d": "Path coverage"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Functionality",
    "Option b": "Usability",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Which of the following is not a quality characteristic listed in ISO 9126 Standard?",
    "Option c": "Supportability",
    "Option d": "Maintainability"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Stub",
    "Option b": "Driver",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "To test a function, the programmer has to write a ____, which calls the function to be tested and passes it test data.",
    "Option c": "Proxy",
    "Option d": "None of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Is the same as equivalence partitioning tests",
    "Option b": "Test boundary condition on, below and above the edges of input and output equivalence classes",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Boundary value testing",
    "Option c": "Test combinations of input circumstances",
    "Option d": "Is used in white box testing strategy"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Quality is job one",
    "Option b": "Zero defects",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Pick the best definition of quality",
    "Option c": "Conformance to requirements",
    "Option d": "Work as designed"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Error condition hiding another error condition",
    "Option b": "Creating a test case which doesn't reveal a fault",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Fault Masking is",
    "Option c": "Maskingn a fault by a developer",
    "Option d": "Masking a fault by a tester"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Lack of technical documentation",
    "Option b": "Lack of test tools on the market for developers",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "One key reason why developers have difficulty testing their own work is:",
    "Option c": "Lack of training",
    "Option d": "Lack of objectivity"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "When the code is complete",
    "Option b": "When the design is complete",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "During the software development process, at what point can the test process start?",
    "Option c": "When the software requirements have been approved",
    "Option d": "When the first code module is ready for unit testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Takes minutes of the meeting",
    "Option b": "Mediates between people",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "In a review meeting a moderator is a person who:",
    "Option c": "Takes telephone calls",
    "Option d": "Write the documents to be reviewed"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Requirements",
    "Option b": "Design",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Acceptance test cases are based on what?",
    "Option c": "Code",
    "Option d": "Decision table"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "This question is impossible to answer",
    "Option b": "This question is easy to answer",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "How much testing is enough?",
    "Option c": "The answer depends on the risk for your industry, contract and special requirements",
    "Option d": "This answer depends on the maturity of your developers"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Statement and branch testing",
    "Option b": "Usability testing",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "A common test technique during component test is:",
    "Option c": "Security testing",
    "Option d": "Performance testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Missing statements",
    "Option b": "Unused branches",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Statement coverage will not check for the following.",
    "Option c": "Dead code",
    "Option d": "Unused statement"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Done by the Developer",
    "Option b": "Done by the Test Engineer",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Independent Verification & Validation is:",
    "Option c": "Done by management",
    "Option d": "Done by an Entity Outside the Project sphere of influence"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Defects",
    "Option b": "Trends analysis",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Code coverage is used as a measure of what?",
    "Option c": "Test effectiveness",
    "Option d": "Time spent testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Component testing",
    "Option b": "Non-functional system testing",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Which of the following uses Impact Analysis most?",
    "Option c": "User acceptance testing",
    "Option d": "Maintenance testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Test Analysis and Design",
    "Option b": "Test Planning and control",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Evaluating testability of the requirements and system are a part of which phase",
    "Option c": "Test Implementation and execution",
    "Option d": "Evaluating exit criteria and reporting"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "Retesting",
    "Option b": "Confirmation testing",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "Repeated Testing of an already tested program, after modification, to discover any defects introduced or uncovered as a result of the changes in the software being tested or in another related or unrelated software component:",
    "Option c": "Regression testing",
    "Option d": "Negetive testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "How much regression testing should be done",
    "Option b": "Exit Criteria",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Impact Analysis helps to decide",
    "Option c": "How many more test cases need to written",
    "Option d": "Different Tools to perform Regression Testing"
  }
]